なんば
Dear, was there something special about today?
お父さん
今日って何の日だっけ？➡
There's a star on the calendar...
ホシ
カレンダーに☆マーク
してあんのよね｡
No clue.
(南波父)さあ…？
何だったかしら…？
What was it for?
ホシ…星…スター？
Star... Star...
Star...
お父さん お昼何食べたい？
Dear, what would you like for lunch?
You're asking about lunch during breakfast?
朝メシ食いながら
もう昼の話か？
It doesn't matter to me.
何でもいいよ｡
うどんでいいよ うどんで…｡
Noodles are fine.
オッケー
(南波母)ＯＫ！➡
Okay.
何の日だったかしら…｡
What was it that was special about today?
I will rise,
climb,
and shoot through the atmosphere
My goal is zero gravity
Space Brothers
Waves of people flood the intersection
Like vague silhouettes they stream past incessantly
How do I look in their midst?
I don't know
Hiding my true intentions desperately
I dish out vague excuses
My ambitions of going to space, harbored for so long,
are frail and brittle
No matter how I turn the globus
I have no home where I end up
There's no point to looking on a map
I will rise,
climb,
and shoot through the atmosphere
until I can look down on the entire world
I will yell
and scream
with a heart of steel
that I am going to zero gravity
#20 The Worst
Possible Punishment
《今日は 閉鎖環境最終日｡➡
"Today is our last day in the sealed box.
とうとう１４日目を迎えた｡➡
Our fourteen days are finally up.
体温･脈拍･血圧ともに異常ナシ｡➡
My weight, pulse, and blood pressure are all normal.
Appetite is normal.
食欲も異常ナシ｡➡
I was concerned about living in a sealed environment, but it's worked out pretty well.
心配していた閉鎖環境だったけど
意外と平気だった｡➡
そして昨日は…》
And yesterday...
Thanks to Nanba's nice idea,
《南波さんの
ナイスアイデアにより➡
we all made noodles together!
みんなで うどんを作った｡➡
今日この日
食べ物があることに感謝しつつ➡
On this final day, I will show my gratitude for the food,
試験最終日を がんばります｡➡
and I will do my very best."
お父さん 応援しててよね｡➡
Dad, cheer for me...
私が必ず 宇宙へ行けるように》
I promise that I will make it into space.
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
Fukuda
Me
Nanba
ふるや
(古谷)ふぅ…くっそ…｡
Damn.
Subject: To Professor Baba Hiroto
｢はじめまして｡
僕は古谷やすしと申します｡➡
"Hello, my name is Furuya Yasushi.
いきなりですが
お礼を言わせてください｡➡
I would like to thank you.
あなた
今回の貴方の開発が
僕のような人間の➡
Your invention convinced me that I shouldn't give up.
どうしようもなかった諦めを
吹き飛ばしてくれました｡➡
Thank you very much!"
本当に ありがとうございます｣｡
To: Furuya Yasushi
｢メールありがとう｡君のような
熱心な人がいてくれて➡
"Thank you for the e-mail.
As an inventor, I am always grateful to hear from passionate people such as yourself.
かんむりょう
僕も技術者として感無量です｡➡
You see, I have always suffered from a complex, much like you have.
実は僕も あなたと同じ
コンプレックスを➡
ずっと抱えていて
宇宙飛行士になる夢を➡
So I was forced to give up my dream of becoming an astronaut.
最初から
諦めざるを得なかったのです｡➡
Please do your absolute best, Furuya.
古谷さん
是非 頑張ってください｡➡
My current dream is to watch someone like you achieve the dream I once harbored."
僕の諦めるしかなかった夢を➡
君のような人に
叶えてもらうことが➡
今の僕の夢なんです｣｡
っしゃ！今日もやるで～｡
Okay, let's do this...
(古谷)太っ！
むった
Thick!
You must have cut these ones.
これ切ったん 南波やな？
Huh?
太すぎんねん！
ほうとう ちゃうねんぞ｡
They're too thick.
We aren't making hoto soup here.
ほうとう？
《太すぎたか…》
Hoto?
So, mine were too thick...
ふくだ
(福田)いただきます｡
いただきま～す｡
Let's eat.
Yes, let's!
うめぇ!!
おいしい！
Super!
This is good...
こりゃいけるね｡
太さがバラバラだけど｡
Not bad at all.
Even if the noodles aren't so uniform.
But if we run out of food in space, we won't be able to stomp the noodles.
でも もし宇宙で
食料不足になっても…➡
うどんは踏めね～な｡
だいさんじ
その前に小麦粉で大惨事や｡
The flour would be a disaster before you even got that far.
(一同)ごちそうさまでした｡
Thank you!
Hello, everyone.
ほしか
(ｽﾋﾟｰｶｰ:星加)それでは 皆さん｡➡
I will now announce your task for the final day.
最終日の
今日の課題を発表します｡➡
今日１日
自由に過ごして下さい｡➡
Please spend the day doing whatever you want.
何をしても構いません｡
それが今日の課題です｡➡
Anything is permitted.
That is your task today.
ただし １６時までに
２人を選んでもらいます｡➡
However, you must have selected two people by 4 PM.
２時間前に
一度 連絡を入れます｡
You will receive a two-hour warning.
自由か…みんなは どうしたい？
Whatever we want?
What does everyone want to do?
とりあえず 今日までやってきた
日課の課題は➡
I'll start by going through all our daily tasks.
最後まで やっとこうや｡
にった
(新田)よし｡
Okay.
７２！
72.
35.
(新田)３５！
156.
１５６！
(新田)１８！
18.
(新田)６２…｡
相変わらず早いな｡
62.
He's always so fast...
15.
304.
(新田)３０４｡
(新田)７！３３！
7.
33.
《どうやって決めればいいんだ…
話し合いで決まんのか？➡
How are we supposed to decide?
By talking about it amongst ourselves?
誰だって自分が一番 宇宙飛行士に
なりたいと思ってるに決まってる》
Everyone here believes that they most want to become an astronaut.
(音声)終了デス｡４３問 正解デス｡
Finish.
Forty-three questions answered correctly.
また最高記録やな｡
Another new record.
《なんで俺らに決めさせんだよ
ジャクサ
ＪＡＸＡは…》
Why did JAXA leave this decision up to us?
This is far worse
《グリーンカードより何より
ひど
これが一番酷い仕打ちだ…》
than those green cards could ever be!
最後のチャンスだぜ お兄ちゃん｡
This is your last chance, big brother.
おう…｡
Right.
《考えるな…誰を選ぶかなんて
今は考えるな》
Don't think...
Don't think about who to choose.
《この課題に集中だ｡
考えるな…》
Focus on the task at hand.
Don't think.
思い出したわ
お父さん｡あの星！➡
I remember what that star is for, dear!
今日 ムッちゃんが
帰ってくる日だ！
Today is the day Mu comes home!
３２５！
326.
562.
５６２！
224.
２２４！
164.
１６４！
２１５！
215.
102.
１０２！１５３！
153.
何やコレ!?どうなってんねん｡
What the hell?
96.
What's going on?
364.
He's even faster without that air abacus.
エアそろばんない方が早いやんけ｡
す すごい…｡
304.
A-Amazing...
432.
522.
５２２！
９００！
900...
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…｡
終了デス｡４９問 正解デス｡
Finish.
Forty-nine questions answered correctly.
《４９問!?》
Forty-nine correct?
《いや たぶん俺のより問題が
簡単だっただけだろう…》
Well, he probably had easier problems than mine.
ウェー ハァ… ウホッ…｡
ハァ…ハァ…ハァ…｡
《何やコイツ…!?》
Wh-What's he doing?
He can barely breathe, and he's reading an American joke book?
《ハァハァ言いながら
アメリカンジョークの本を…》
ハァ…ハァ…｡
(古谷)おい｡
Hey!
何かあったんか ジブン｡
何もねぇよ…｡
Did something happen?
Nope.
(新田)しょうがねえ｡➡
Fine...
今日から｢南波｣って
呼んでやるよ｡
Starting today, I'll call you "Nanba".
っつっても 今日で終わりだけど｡
Though it's also our final day.
Okay.
ＯＫ｡
《…にしても 何だったんだ
さっきの あの集中力…》
But back there,
how could he be so focused?
みぞぐち
まかべ
(溝口)真壁さん｡
Makabe...
(溝口)僕の所にグリーンカードが
来てれば➡
Had I received a green card earlier,
あんな風には
ならなかったですよ｡
none of this would have ever happened.
真壁さんを疑うことは
なかったんです｡
I never would have suspected you...
ふぅ…もういいよ 別に｡➡
It's water under the bridge.
それより 昨日から
何 一生懸命やってんの？それ｡
Anyway, what have you been so hard at work on?
わかるでしょ？みんなの得点を
再計算してたんですよ｡
You've probably already guessed.
I'm reconstructing everyone's scores.
初日からの記憶をたどって
数値を入力していきました｡
I've been entering all the numbers from memory.
とみい
幸い 富井君が かなり詳細に
覚えていてくれて助かりました｡➡
Fortunately, Tomii remembers most of the details...
He's been a big help.
｢またか｣って
思うかもしれませんけど➡
You're probably questioning my decision,
but I don't see how we can settle anything without these scores.
これなしでは話にならないと
僕は思ってるんです｡➡
目に見える｢差｣が
必要なんですよ｡➡
We need a tangible metric.
If we got too close, the decision would only be more difficult.
仲良しこよしでは決めづらくなる
だけだと思ってました｡➡
Makabe, who do you imagine in first place?
真壁さん 今１位は
誰だと思います？
てしま
(溝口)手島さんです｡
It's Teshima.
(溝口)意外ですよね…｡➡
Surprising, isn't it?
At the beginning, he must have been holding back.
彼は途中まで わざと力を
抑えてたんでしょうか？➡
それで 真壁さん
今あなたは 残念ながら…｡
And, Makabe,
I'm sorry to say that you're currently...
ゴミあったら言ってね～｡
Let me know if you have any trash.
来た時よりも美しくね～｡
We want to leave this place cleaner than when we arrived...
あ～!?何やて～？
Eh?
What was that?
⦅あの…南波さん⦆
Um, Nanba?
⦅私の名前 下の名前で
呼んでくれていいですよ⦆
You can call me by my first name.
Huh? C-Can I really?
⦅えっ…い い いいんですか？⦆
Yes.
⦅はい｡自分の名前
気に入ってるんです⦆
I happen to like my name.
(福田)⦅もし君が
その理由に気づいたら➡
If you're able to figure out why I did what I did,
then when you do,
その時は…握手でもしよう⦆
I'll shake your hand.
⦅福田さん！⦆
Fukuda...
⦅よかった！⦆
It's an honor.
⦅ありがと！⦆
Thank you.
If you beat me in the next task,
⦅次の課題で俺に勝てたら
呼んであげるよ お兄ちゃん⦆
I'll use your first name, big brother.
⦅ポウ！⦆
⦅ヒィ!!⦆
⦅ホワッチャー!!ワチャ！⦆
⦅うう～ん｡他の指令に
変えてくんねぇかな…⦆
Man, I hope they give me a different order...
⦅わかってるやろな｡
｢やっさん｣やぞ！｢やっさん｣➡
Got it?
It's Ya! Ya!
アクセントは｢さ｣のとこや！⦆
⦅わかったって！⦆
You gotta be polite!
I get it already.
⦅これは ただの賭けとちゃう｡
どっちが宇宙飛行士に➡
This is no ordinary bet...
This is a battle to determine who would make a better astronaut.
ふさわ
相応しいか ちょっとでも
優劣つけとくためのバトルや！⦆
⦅アッハハハ…福田さん…⦆
Crap!
《楽しかったな～ この２週間…》
These two weeks have been
really fun...
《こうしてみると…すごく
いいメンバーだった》
Looking back, this was a great team.
《色々あったな…》
A lot happened.
《変なヤツばっかやったけど…》
Every single member was a weirdo.
《この５人が…５人とも
宇宙へ行けたら…》
If all five...
If only all five of us could go to space...
It's time, everyone.
時間です｡皆さん｡
どんな方法でも構いません｡➡
You're free to use any method you wish.
２時間以内に
２人を選んで下さい｡
In the next two hours, please select two members.
ハァ～｡
(原田)マメだな～｡
He's really diligent...
よ～し ピッカピカ！
Okay, squeaky clean.
これで もう拭くとこねぇや｡
あ～きれいっ！
Nothing left for us to wipe.
Shiny...
(新田)向こうも終わったよ｡
We're done with our side.
(福田)じゃあ みんな
中も きれいになったし➡
Okay, everyone...
We've cleaned up the place,
時間も迫ってきてる…
今から２人を選ぼう｡
and we're running out of time.
Let's choose our two people.
そうだな｡
Right.
あっ ううっ…ごめん｡
S-S-Sorry...
ちょっと…その前にトイレ｡
I need to use the restroom first.
はよせ～よ｡
マッハや マッハ！
Hurry it up... Make it snappy.
問題は決める方法だな｡全員が
同意できるってのが必要条件か｡
We should figure out how we'll decide,
given that we need to reach a unanimous decision.
私も ずっと考えていたが…
これといって いい案がない｡
I've been mulling it over, but I don't have any good ideas.
《私は自分が
劣っているとは思わない…➡
I don't believe that I'm an inferior candidate...
この５人なら誰だろうと…》
All five members are worthy.
《誰がなっても
おかしくない…この５人なら》
All five members are qualified...
《そんな中で誰かを選らばなきゃ
ならないわけだから➡
But we're forced to choose,
イヤでも考えてしまう…
みんなの“弱み"を…➡
which really gets you thinking...
What is each person's own liability?
それを言ったら明らかに
不利になる人が２人いる》
That puts two members at a disadvantage.
《やっぱり不安だ…考えだしたら
急に肩身が狭くなってきた➡
I'm really worried...
The more I think about it, the less confident I feel.
私だけ みんなと違う…》
Because I'm the only one with an unusual motivation.
(福田)《伊東さんは近い将来
なくなるかもしれない➡
Itou desires to board the ISS, which is slated for retirement soon.
ＩＳＳへの搭乗を
希望していることが…➡
That puts her behind the others.
他のみんなとの大きな差…
｢必要性｣という点で➡
After all, she wouldn't be as useful in the long run.
ごて
後手に捉えられても仕方ない｡
そして…私もだ｡➡
I'm in the same position.
若さを留めたつもりでも
実年齢は変えられない》
I've done my best to stay youthful, but I can't change my age.
《｢飛行士に
さき
なってからの未来の短さ｣➡
After becoming an astronaut, I just won't have as much time.
話し合いで決めるとなれば
必ず 誰かにそこをつかれて➡
If there's a discussion,
this point will be brought up,
まず 初めに私が除外される…》
and I'll be dropped from consideration.
まあ 普通に考えて一番
自然なんは…“投票"かな やっぱ➡
Well,
the most obvious method would be a simple vote.
それぞれ
自分以外の２人の名前書いて…➡
We all write down two people's names that aren't our own.
それを集計した
トップ２人で決定やん！
And we'll select the two with the most votes.
俺は投票には賛成できね～な…
ウソつけるだろ｡投票だと➡
I don't think we should hold a vote...
People can lie.
And you can always vote for someone unlikely to win,
人気が集まりそうな奴に わざと
票を入れないってこともできる｡➡
to boost your own chances.
自分が残るためにな｡
俺なら そうするし…➡
That's what I'd do.
And I'm sure that
そうしてでも選ばれたいのは
みんな同じだろ…｡
to be chosen, everyone else would do the same.
《くそ…ＪＡＸＡが
見たいものはわかった…➡
Damn...
I understand what JAXA's looking for.
こういう時 誰かを切り捨てる
非情さを持てるかどうかだ…➡
They want to see if we're ready to make necessary sacrifices.
They want us to say that Fukuda is too old compared to the others.
｢福田さんは 年だから
優先できない｣って➡
はっきり言うべきなんだ…イヤ
それともバカげてるけど➡
Well...
We could always let luck decide.
｢運｣だけで決める方法もある…
どっちが正しいんだ…》
Which would be the right way?
じゃあ そういうのなしで ちゃんと
自分の思うところを書こうや！
《正しい方法は…》
Then put your ideas down on paper!
What is the correct method?
⦅迷った時はね
｢どっちが正しいか｣なんて➡
When in doubt, don't worry over what's right.
考えちゃダメよ｡
日が暮れちゃうわ⦆
Summer Vacation Independent Project
You'll run out of time.
Huh? Then what do I do?
⦅エエーッ？
じゃあ どうすんのさ⦆
⦅頭で考えなきゃいいのよ｡
答えは もっと下…⦆
Don't use your head.
You'll find the answer lower.
⦅んんっ!?⦆
⦅ほら ムッタ 下げて 下げて…⦆
Come on, Mutta. Lower your hands...
⦅んんっ!?⦆
⦅あなたのことなら
あなたの胸が知ってるもんよ⦆
Your heart knows what's right.
⦅ん…⦆
⦅｢どっちが楽しいか｣で
決めなさい⦆
Choose the answer that will be fun.
どうすんねん！
投票がアカンのやったら➡
What should we do?
If we aren't gonna vote, do you have a better idea?
何か他に ええ案あるんか？
しゃ～ないなぁ
消去法しかないか…｡
Fine, then...
We'll use process of elimination.
≪みんな！≫
Everyone...
ジャンケンで決めようか｡
Let's decide with rock-paper-scissors.
Huh?
What?!
ふざけてるワケじゃね～ぞ…
マジで言ってんだ｡
This isn't a joke.
I'm serious.
アホか ありえへん！
却下や！却下！➡
Idiot, that's totally ridiculous!
ここまで来て
なんで ジャンケンやねん！
ジャンケン…｡
After all that, you want to use rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors...
I don't get it.
(古谷)意味わからへん！お前
頭の中までパンチパｰマか！
(福田)《南波君…➡
Is your head fuzzy on the inside, too?
Nanba...
君は 僕らにもチャンスを…？》
You're giving us a chance?
(茄子田)ほぉ～ジャンケンか…
彼らしいね…ねぇ…ねぇ｡
Rock-paper-scissors, huh?
That sounds just like him...
Yes...
Yes.
俺はジャンケンでも いいぜ｡
I'm okay with rock-paper-scissors.
Huh?
(新田)イカサマがない分
投票よりはマシだ｡
There won't be any cheating, like there could be in a vote.
何 言うてんねん ジブンまで！
Hey, do you hear what you're saying?
ＪＡＸＡも
何人か選ぶっつってたろ｡➡
JAXA said they would select multiple candidates.
要するに ここで
選ばれなかった者の中から➡
Meaning that they'll be considering those who aren't chosen in this stage.
欲しい人間を残すわけだ｡
本当に必要とされる者なら➡
If they really want you,
ここでの結果にかかわらず
選ばれる…｡
you'll be selected, regardless of what happens here.
ありえへん…！こんな大事な…
人生を左右する選択を➡
I don't believe it...
It makes zero sense
to let rock-paper-scissors make a decision that affects your entire life!
ジャンケンなんかで
決めて ええわけないやろ!!
この手帳 見てくれ！➡
Look at this notepad!
みんなが この２週間でやった
全課題の成績が記録してある！
I've spent the past two weeks recording everyone's scores at each task!
ちゃんと正直に書いた！
みんな 順位知りたいやろ！
I was objective!
I'm sure you're curious about ranks... I can tell you right now.
何位か 発表しよか！
まず 俺はな…➡
I'll start with myself.
I'm...
俺は…くっ…➡
最下位や｡
in last place...
最下位やったわ…俺！
やっさん…｡
I was dead last...
Ya...
もう 俺の中ではな
２人は決まってんねん！➡
I already know the two people I'm picking...
どう考えても
この２人しかありえへん！
It only makes sense to choose them! Wanna know who?!
言おか!?
(新田)いいよ…言わなくて｡
It's fine.
You don't need to tell us.
はぁ…はぁ…｡
そうだよ｡
Yeah.
それより やっさん…前に
もっとスルドイこと言ってただろ｡
Anyway, Ya,
you said something really smart the other day.
⦅ジャンケンを超える
公平な方法はあらへん！⦆
ジャンケンを超える➡
Rock-paper-scissors is the fairest way to decide.
That rock-paper-scissors is the fairest way to decide.
公平な方法はない！って｡
Don't whine if you lose, Nanba.
この５人は まあ…アレだ｡
The five of us are... Well...
み～んな
ジャンケンみたいなもんだ➡
We're kind of like rock-paper-scissors.
You have members who are rock,
グーみたいな奴がいて…➡
チョキみたいな奴もいて…➡
members who are scissors,
パーみたいな奴もいる…➡
and members who are paper.
誰が一番強いか
答えを知ってる奴いるか？
Does anyone really know the strongest candidate?
(古谷)くそっ…｡
Damn...
(古谷)後悔せ～へんな…➡
You'd better not regret this.
ジャンケンを超える
公平な方法はあらへん…➡
Rock-paper-scissors is the fairest way to decide...
負けても文句いうなよ 南波！
おう｡
So don't whine if you lose,
Nanba.
Yeah.
こんな人生を賭けた
ジャンケンは初めてだな…ハハッ｡
I'd never guess that rock-paper-scissors would change my life.
私もです｡
I agree.
(原田)始まるぞ｡
They're about to start...
皆さん ２週間
ありがとうございました！
Everyone, I want to thank you for the past two weeks.
これで やっと終わる…｡
It's finally over.
(一同)せ～の！
ジャンケン…➡
Ready, set...
Rock...
Paper...
ホイ！
Scissors!
The lens inside my eyes
went completely out of focus when I saw you
The signs of love flooded the occipital lobe of my cerebrum
The words the left side of my brain produced
brought my vocal cords to reverberation
Vigorously my confession traversed my tongue
May I love you?
May I really love you?
May I be beside you? (The concentration of my hormones rose)
(Dopamine overwhelmed me)
Can I hold your hand? (My blood circulation powered up)
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#21 A Long-Awaited
Glimpse of the Sky
＜人生を賭けた
私達のジャンケン＞
A game of rock-paper-scissors changes our lives!
＜勝負は たった一回で決まった＞
One round was all it took.
＜六太君 あの結果が出た今
君は何を思う？＞
Mutta, how do you feel now?
＜そして 閉鎖環境での生活を
ようやく終えた私は➡
And after leaving the sealed environment,
ついに せりかさんと
食事をすることに！＞
I finally get to eat out with Serika...
＜いや～！嬉しすぎるぜ＞
Yes! I'm so happy!
Right, let's eat out.
(福田)＜さあ 食事だ＞
(新田)＜行くか＞
Come on.
Yeah, they'll be there, too.
＜ああ この人達もいたんだ＞
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"A Long-Awaited Glimpse of the Sky"
If only it were just the two of us...
＜２人っきりなら
どんなに素敵だったか＞
ひびと
(日々人)パンパカパーン！
This Week's Space Photo
This week's space photo!
今週の宇宙写真です！
スッゲェ～｡
Awesome!